{
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "Question 1 : What is the capital of Australia?",
        "options": ["Sydney", "Melbourne", "Canberra", "Perth"],
        "answer": "Canberra"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 2 : What is the capital of Brazil?",
        "options": ["Rio de Janeiro", "Brasília", "São Paulo", "Salvador"],
        "answer": "Brasília"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 3 : What is the capital of Canada?",
        "options": ["Toronto", "Vancouver", "Ottawa", "Montreal"],
        "answer": "Ottawa"
      },
      {
        "question": "Qustion 4 : What is the capital of China?",
        "options": ["Shanghai", "Beijing", "Hong Kong", "Guangzhou"],
        "answer": "Beijing"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 5 : What is the capital of Egypt?",
        "options": ["Alexandria", "Cairo", "Giza", "Luxor"],
        "answer": "Cairo"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 6 : What is the capital of Germany?",
        "options": ["Munich", "Berlin", "Frankfurt", "Hamburg"],
        "answer": "Berlin"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 7 : What is the capital of India?",
        "options": ["Mumbai", "New Delhi", "Bangalore", "Chennai"],
        "answer": "New Delhi"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 8 : What is the capital of Japan?",
        "options": ["Osaka", "Kyoto", "Tokyo", "Nagoya"],
        "answer": "Tokyo"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 9 : What is the capital of Russia?",
        "options": ["Saint Petersburg", "Moscow", "Novosibirsk", "Yekaterinburg"],
        "answer": "Moscow"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 10 : What is the capital of South Korea?",
        "options": ["Busan", "Incheon", "Seoul", "Daegu"],
        "answer": "Seoul"
      }
    ]
  }
  